Guide to the Duke Mathematical Journal Records, 1924-1985 UA.24.27.0031
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke Mathematical Journal records
1924-1988
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Duke Mathematical Journal
Duke University. University Archives
UA.24.27.0031
27 Linear Feet About 19,000 items.
This collection is largely comprised of correspondence of the individuals and organizations who communicated with the editors of the Duke Mathematical Journal. All correspondence related to accepted papers was kept, as well as a significant amount of correspondence related to rejected papers before 1970. Referee reports are also included, as well as billing and correspondence between the Journal and various publishing houses. Topics covered include edits to papers, requests for offprint copies, correspondence between editors, correspondence with the American Mathematical Society, and the Journal's budget and funding. The collection ends with a series of record books recording each paper received and reviewed by the Journal.
Biographical/Historical note
The Duke Mathematical Journal was founded in 1934 and published its first issue in 1935. Its founding was brought about in large part by the American Mathematical Society's encouraging Duke University to establish a mathematical journal. In 1927, and again in 1931, the Society urged the University to create a journal, stating that the need for a new mathematical periodical existed. Furthermore, it argued that in order to attract papers from leading mathematicians, such a periodical would need assured financial support to guarantee its permanent existence, and that Duke University was in a strategic position to embark on such a project.
Since its founding, the Duke Mathematical Journal has been one of the leading mathematical journals. Without specializing in a small number of subject areas, it emphasizes the most active and influential areas of current mathematics. Of the more than 600 mathematics journals published worldwide, only 277 reach the level of impact required to be included in the rankings of the Institute for Scientific Information. The Duke Mathematical Journal is consistently among the top ranking journals, with an impact factor of 1.701 and a cited half-life of >10, the highest score given in this category.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is organized into thirteen distinct series.
The first series is collated alphabetical files based upon the first letter of the subject, or the individual's last name. Each folder covers a year or a range of years, and each letter of the alphabet has five such folders, running from latest to earliest. Individual subject files for particularly prominent individuals and organizations are interspersed within the general alphabetical folders, and maintain roughly alphabetical order.
Series 2-7 are alphabetical files similar to the first series, with the difference that each letter of the alphabet recieved one folder covering a longer range of years, rather than several smaller folders for each letters. Subject files are interspersed alphabetically within series 2-3 as in series 1.
Series 8 is assorted subject files related to the period covered by series 4-7, where the subject files ceased to be interspersed throughout the series.
Series 9 represents a shift in the organizational structure, moving to a numeric system. As papers were submitted to the Journal, each was assigned a number and filed in chronological order, with any future correspondence related to that paper attached or stapled to the original piece of correspondence.
Series 10 retains the numerical structure of series 9, but adds two initial digits to each number signifying the year in which a paper was received.
Series 11 is also a numeric system, but the digits comprising the numbers changed in their significance. The first digit represents the last digit of the year (i.e. 1981 is 1, 1982 is 2, etc.). The next two digits signify the month the paper was received (01 represents January, 12 represents December). The following two digits represent the day of reception, while the last digit represents the order in which multiple papers were reviewed on that day. Thus, a paper with the number 104060 indicates that the paper was received on April 6th, 1981, and was the first paper to be processed that day.
Series 12 is comprised of miscellaneous correspondence unrelated to specific papers divided by year.
Series 13 is a series of record books documenting reception and processing of papers, and are in order by year.
Provenance
The Duke Mathematics Journal records were received by the Duke University Archives as a transfer from 1982 to 1990.
Collection Overview
This collection is largely comprised of correspondence of the individuals and organizations who communicated with the editors of the Duke Mathematical Journal. All correspondence related to accepted papers was kept, as well as a significant amount of correspondence related to rejected papers before 1970. Referee reports are also included, as well as billing and correspondence between the Journal and various publishing houses. Topics covered include edits to papers, requests for offprint copies, correspondence between editors, correspondence with the American Mathematical Society, and the Journal's budget and funding. The collection ends with a series of record books recording each paper received and reviewed by the Journal.
The collection is organized into thirteen distinct series.
The first series is collated alphabetical files based upon the first letter of the subject, or the individual's last name. Each folder covers a year or a range of years, and each letter of the alphabet has five such folders, running from latest to earliest. Individual subject files for particularly prominent individuals and organizations are interspersed within the general alphabetical folders, and maintain roughly alphabetical order.
Series 2-7 are alphabetical files similar to the first series, with the difference that each letter of the alphabet recieved one folder covering a longer range of years, rather than several smaller folders for each letters. Subject files are interspersed alphabetically within series 2-3 as in series 1.
Series 8 is assorted subject files related to the period covered by series 4-7, where the subject files ceased to be interspersed throughout the series.
Series 9 represents a shift in the organizational structure, moving to a numeric system. As papers were submitted to the Journal, each was assigned a number and filed in chronological order, with any future correspondence related to that paper attached or stapled to the original piece of correspondence.
Series 10 retains the numerical structure of series 9, but adds two initial digits to each number signifying the year in which a paper was received.
Series 11 is also a numeric system, but the digits comprising the numbers changed in their significance. The first digit represents the last digit of the year (i.e. 1981 is 1, 1982 is 2, etc.). The next two digits signify the month the paper was received (01 represents January, 12 represents December). The following two digits represent the day of reception, while the last digit represents the order in which multiple papers were reviewed on that day. Thus, a paper with the number 104060 indicates that the paper was received on April 6th, 1981, and was the first paper to be processed that day.
Series 12 is comprised of miscellaneous correspondence unrelated to specific papers divided by year.
Series 13 is a series of record books documenting reception and processing of papers, and are in order by year.
Mathematics -- Periodicals.; Duke University. Duke Mathematical Journal; American Mathematical Society; Duke University. University Archives; Duke University Press
- Collated Alphabetical Subject Files by Year, 1934-1944; 1
  - Annals of Mathematics, 1934-1936 (Box 1)
  - Author's Manual, Undated (Box 1)
  - Author's Manual - Fan Mail, 1939 October-November (Box 1)
  - A (general), 1943 (Box 1)
  - A (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - A (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - A (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - A (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - Banta Publishing Company, 1938-1939 (Box 1)
  - Banta Publishing Company Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 1)
  - William Byrd Press, 1943 (Box 1)
  - William Byrd Press, 1942 March-November (Box 1)
  - B (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - B (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - B (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - B (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - Ba-Bo (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - Bo-Bu (general), 1934-1936 (Box 1)
  - Centenniel Reprints, Undated (Box 1)
  - Covers, etc., 1935, March (Box 1)
  - C (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - C (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - C (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - C (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - Ca-Cl (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - Co-Cu (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - Duke University Press, 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - Duke University Press, 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - Duke University Press, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Duke University Press, 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - D (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - D (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - D (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - D (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - D (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - E (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - E (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - E (general), 1939 February-September (Box 1)
  - E (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - E (general), 1936 (Box 1)
  - Exhanges, 1934-1938 (Box 1)
  - Exchange Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 1)
  - Exchanges, 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - J. H. Furst Company, 1939 January-February (Box 1)
  - F (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - F (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - F (general), 1939 January-September (Box 1)
  - F (general), 1938 (Box 1)
  - F (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - G (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - G (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - G (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - G (general), 1937-1938 (Box 1)
  - G (general), 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - H (general), 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - H (general), 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - H (general), 1939 (Box 1)
  - H (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - H (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - I (general), 1943 March-November (Box 2)
  - I (general), 1940 January (Box 2)
  - I (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - J (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - J (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - J (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - J (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - J (general), 1936 (Box 2)
  - K (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - K (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - K (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - K (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - K (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - L (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - L (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - L (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - L (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - L (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - Mc (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - Mc (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - Mc (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - Mc (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - Mc (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - Mathematical Journal, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - Mathematical Association, 1939 March-December (Box 2)
  - Mathematical Journal, 1938 November (Box 2)
  - M (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - M (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - M (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - M (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - M (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - N (general), 1943 April-September (Box 2)
  - N (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - N (general), 1939 October-November (Box 2)
  - N (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - O (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - O (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - O (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - O (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - O (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - P (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - P (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - P (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - P (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - P (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - Q (general), 1937 January-September (Box 2)
  - Q (general), 1936 October (Box 2)
  - R (general), 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - R (general), 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - R (general), 1939 (Box 2)
  - R (general), 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - R (general), 1935-1936 (Box 2)
  - Referee Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 2)
  - Referee Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 2)
  - Referee Reports, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Referee Reports, 1937-1938 (Box 3)
  - Referee Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 3)
  - Referee Reports A-M, 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - Referee Reports N-Z, 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - Reprint Order Blanks, Undated (Box 3)
  - Subscription Campaign, 1936-1939 (Box 3)
  - Subscription Campaign Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 3)
  - S (general), 1942-1943 (Box 3)
  - S (general) [1 of 2], 1939-1941 (Box 3)
  - S (general) [2 of 2], 1940-1941 (Box 3)
  - S (general), 1939 (Box 3)
  - S (general), 1937-1938 (Box 3)
  - S (general), 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - T (general), 1942-1943 (Box 3)
  - T (general), 1940-1941 (Box 3)
  - T (general), 1939 (Box 3)
  - T (general), 1937-1938 (Box 3)
  - T (general), 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - U (general), 1940 June-July (Box 3)
  - U (general), 1939 March-July (Box 3)
  - U (general), 1938 April (Box 3)
  - V (general), 1943 March-November (Box 3)
  - V (general), 1940-1941 (Box 3)
  - V (general), 1939 (Box 3)
  - V (general), 1937-1938 (Box 3)
  - V (general), 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press - Acknowledgement, 1942 January-July (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press - Alterations, 1942 February-June (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press - Bills, 1935-1942 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1942-1943 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1941 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1940 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1939 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1938 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press, 1937 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press [1 of 2], 1935-1936 (Box 3)
  - Waverly Press [2 of 2], 1934-1935 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1944 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1943 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1942 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1941 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1940 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1939 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1938 (Box 3)
  - D.V. Widder, 1937 (Box 3)
  - W (general), 1942-1943 (Box 4)
  - W (general), 1940-1941 (Box 4)
  - W (general), 1939 (Box 4)
  - W (general), 1937-1938 (Box 4)
  - W (general), 1935-1936 (Box 4)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1942-1943 (Box 4)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1940-1941 (Box 4)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1939 (Box 4)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1937-1938 (Box 4)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1935-1936 (Box 4)
- Alphabetical Series, 1926-1963, bulk 1944-1951; 2
  - Addendum - Author's Manual, 1942 November (Box 4)
  - American Mathematical Society Announcement of Journal Rates, 1951 July-October (Box 4)
  - A (general), 1944-1952 (Box 4)
  - Budget, 1936-1947 (Box 4)
  - Ba-Bi (general) [1 of 2], 1944-1961 (Box 4)
  - Ba-Bi (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - Bi-By (general) [1 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - Bi-By (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - R.P. Boas, Jr., 1944-1951 (Box 4)
  - C (general) [1 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - C (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - Covers, 1938-1941 (Box 4)
  - H.S.M. Coxeter, 1944-1951 (Box 4)
  - Duplicated Sheets, Undated (Box 4)
  - D (general), 1944-1962 (Box 4)
  - Department of State, 1944-1946 (Box 4)
  - Duke Mathematical Magazine, 1941 (Box 4)
  - Duke University Press, 1944-1951 (Box 4)
  - Equipment, 1940-1951 (Box 4)
  - E (general), 1947-1958 (Box 4)
  - Editorial Board, 1941-1943 (Box 4)
  - Founding, 1927-1935 (Box 4)
  - F (general), 1944-1963 (Box 4)
  - G (general) [1 of 2], 1945-1962 (Box 5)
  - G (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 5)
  - L.J. Green, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - G.A. Hedlund, 1945-1951 (Box 5)
  - Ha-He (general) [1 of 2], 1944-1961 (Box 5)
  - Ha-He (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1959 (Box 5)
  - Hi-Hu (general) [1 of 2], 1944-1961 (Box 5)
  - Hi-Hu (general) [2 of 2], 1944-1962 (Box 5)
  - Setting of Indices, 1936 June-November (Box 5)
  - I (general), 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - J (general), 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Irving Kaplansky, 1949-1952 (Box 5)
  - K (general) [1 of 2], 1946-1952 (Box 5)
  - K (general) [2 of 2], 1945-1953 (Box 5)
  - Letter to Members of Association, 1942 March 4 (Box 5)
  - R.E. Langer, 1951 February-December (Box 5)
  - N. Levinson, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Library (Miss Merrit, et. al.), 1946-1950 (Box 5)
  - Loomis, L. H., 1948-1951 (Box 5)
  - L (general), 1944-1952 (Box 5)
  - C.C. MacDuffee, 1944-1950 (Box 5)
  - M.L. MacQueen, 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - McCoy, N.H., 1945-1951 (Box 5)
  - E.J. McShane, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Mc (general), 1950-1952 (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts Returned, 1944-1946 (Box 5)
  - W.T. Martin, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Matrices, 1935-1942 (Box 5)
  - F. J. Murray, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Ma-Mi (general), 1944-1952 (Box 5)
  - Mi-Mu (general), 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Preperation of Manuscripts, etc., 1926-1943 (Box 5)
  - N (general), 1944-1952 (Box 5)
  - O (general), 1945-1951 (Box 5)
  - Gordon Pall, 1944-1951 (Box 5)
  - Harry Pollard, 1944-1949 (Box 5)
  - P (general), 1944-1952 (Box 6)
  - Tibor Rado, 1944-1948 (Box 6)
  - R (general), 1944-1952 (Box 6)
  - R. Salem, 1944-1951 (Box 6)
  - Subscription Blanks, 1935-1950 (Box 6)
  - Sa-Sh (general), 1944-1952 (Box 6)
  - Si-Sz (general), 1944-1952 (Box 6)
  - J.M. Thomas, 1944-1949 (Box 6)
  - John Tuckey, 1944-1951 (Box 6)
  - T (general), 1944-1952 (Box 6)
  - U (general), 1949-1951 (Box 6)
  - V (general), 1946-1950 (Box 6)
  - L.I. Wade, 1944-1951 (Box 6)
  - Morgan Ward, 1944-1945 (Box 6)
  - Waverly Reprints, 1934-1941 (Box 6)
  - G.T. Whyburn, 1944-1947 (Box 6)
  - Widder, D.V., 1949-1951 (Box 6)
  - Widder, D.V., 1947-1948 (Box 6)
  - Widder, D.V., 1945-1946 (Box 6)
  - H.S. Well, 1944-1945 (Box 6)
  - W (general), 1949-1952 (Box 6)
  - W (general), 1944-1948 (Box 6)
  - William Byrd Press, 1947-1951 (Box 6)
  - William Byrd Press Bills, 1947-1951 (Box 6)
  - Waverly Press Bills, 1942-1947 (Box 6)
  - William Byrd Press, 1944-1946 (Box 6)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1947-1951 (Box 6)
- Alphabetical Series, 1950-1966, bulk 1952-1958; 3
  - A (general), 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - Administration Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 7)
  - R. P. Boas, Jr., 1952-1953 (Box 7)
  - Budget, 1950-1959 (Box 7)
  - B (general) [1 of 4], 1953-1958 (Box 7)
  - B (general) [2 of 4], 1953-1957 (Box 7)
  - B (general) [3 of 4], 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - B (general) [4 of 4], 1952-1954 (Box 7)
  - C (general) [1 of 2], 1952-1958 (Box 7)
  - C (general) [2 of 2], 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - D (general) [1 of 2], 1954-1957 (Box 7)
  - D (general) [2 of 2], 1952-1958 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Press, 1951-1954 (Box 7)
  - E (general), 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - F (general), 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1952-1954 (Box 7)
  - Free Mailing List, 1953-1958 (Box 7)
  - G (general) [1 of 2], 1954-1957 (Box 7)
  - G (general) [2 of 2], 1951-1957 (Box 7)
  - H (general) [1 of 4], 1953-1958 (Box 7)
  - H (general) [2 of 4], 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - H (general) [3 of 4], 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - H (general) [4 of 4], 1952-1953 (Box 7)
  - Information Exchange with Maurice Hiens (etc.), 1964-1966 (Box 7)
  - Inventory of Back Volumes, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
  - I (general), 1952-1957 (Box 7)
  - Journal Advertisement, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
  - J (general), 1952-1958 (Box 7)
  - Irving Kaplansky, 1952-1954 (Box 7)
  - K (general) [1 of 2], 1953-1957 (Box 8)
  - K (general) [2 of 2], 1952-1957 (Box 8)
  - L (general) [1 of 2], 1953-1957 (Box 8)
  - L (general) [2 of 2], 1952-1958 (Box 8)
  - Langer, R.E., 1952-1957 (Box 8)
  - Mc (general), 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - N.H. McCoy, 1952-1955 (Box 8)
  - M (general), 1952-1958 (Box 8)
  - Meeting w/ Duke University Press Committee, 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous Requests, 1954-1964 (Box 8)
  - N (general), 1952-1957 (Box 8)
  - O (general), 1952-1955 (Box 8)
  - P (general), 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - Printing Costs, 1952 June-July (Box 8)
  - Printing Costs, 1952-1963 (Box 8)
  - R (general) [1 of 2], 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - R (general) [2 of 2], 1952-1954 (Box 8)
  - S-Sh (general), 1952-1958 (Box 8)
  - Si-Sz (general), 1952-1958 (Box 8)
  - T (general), 1952-1955 (Box 8)
  - U (general), 1953-1954 (Box 8)
  - V (general), 1952-1954 (Box 8)
  - W-Wh (general), 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - Wi-Wy (general), 1951-1956 (Box 8)
  - William Byrd Press, 1952-1954 (Box 8)
  - William Byrd Press Bills, 1952-1953 (Box 8)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1952-1955 (Box 8)
  - Form Letters, Old Procedures, Undated (Box 8)
- Alphabetical Series, 1954-1968; 4
  - A (general), 1957-1967 (Box 9)
  - B (general) [1 of 2], 1957-1968 (Box 9)
  - B (general) [2 of 2], 1959-1968 (Box 9)
  - C (general) [1 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 9)
  - C (general) [2 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 9)
  - C (general) [3 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 9)
  - D (general), 1961-1968 (Box 9)
  - E (general), 1961-1968 (Box 9)
  - F (general), 1958-1968 (Box 9)
  - G (general) [1 of 2], 1962-1968 (Box 9)
  - G (general) [2 of 2], 1962-1968 (Box 9)
  - H (general) [1 of 2], 1961-1968 (Box 9)
  - H (general) [2 of 2], 1963-1968 (Box 9)
  - I (general), 1957-1968 (Box 9)
  - J (general), 1958-1968 (Box 9)
  - K (general) [1 of 2], 1957-1968 (Box 9)
  - K (general) [2 of 2], 1956-1966 (Box 9)
  - L (general) [1 of 2], 1958-1967 (Box 10)
  - L (general) [2 of 2], 1958-1968 (Box 10)
  - Mc (general), 1956-1968 (Box 10)
  - George W. Mackey, 1956-1963 (Box 10)
  - M (general) [1 of 2], 1958-1966 (Box 10)
  - M (general) [2 of 2], 1958-1968 (Box 10)
  - N (general), 1957-1968 (Box 10)
  - O (general), 1957-1968 (Box 10)
  - P (general) [1 of 3], 1961-1969 (Box 10)
  - P (general) [2 of 3], 1956-1968 (Box 10)
  - P (general) [3 of 3], 1956-1967 (Box 10)
  - Q (general), 1964 March (Box 10)
  - R (general) [1 of 4], 1956 -1958 (Box 10)
  - R (general) [2 of 4], 1956-1968 (Box 10)
  - R (general) [3 of 4], 1958-1967 (Box 10)
  - R ( general) [4 of 4], 1954-1968 (Box 10)
  - Sa-Sh (general) [1 of 3], 1959-1968 (Box 10)
  - Sa-Sh (general) [2 of 3], 1956-1967 (Box 10)
  - Sa-Sh (general) [3 of 3], 1957-1967 (Box 10)
  - Si-Sy (general) [1 of 3], 1956-1968 (Box 10)
  - Si-Sy (general) [2 of 3], 1956-1968 (Box 11)
  - Si-Sy (general) [3 of 3], 1960-1968 (Box 11)
  - T (general) [1 of 2], 1960-1968 (Box 11)
  - T (general) [2 of 2], 1960-1967 (Box 11)
  - U (general), 1958-1968 (Box 11)
  - V (general), 1955-1967 (Box 11)
  - W-Wh (general) [1 of 2], 1956-1967 (Box 11)
  - W-Wh (general) [2 of 2], 1957-1967 (Box 11)
  - Wi-Wy (general), 1955-1967 (Box 11)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1956-1967 (Box 11)
- Alphabetical Series, 1955-1969, bulk 1965-1969; 5
  - A (general), 1955-1968 (Box 11)
  - B (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - C (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - D (general), 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - E (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - F (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - G (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - H (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - I (general), 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - J (general), 1968-1969 (Box 11)
  - K (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - L (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - Mc (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - M (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - N (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - O (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - P-Q (general), 1964-1969 (Box 11)
  - R (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - S (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - T (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - U-V (general), 1966-1969 (Box 11)
  - W (general), 1965-1969 (Box 11)
  - X, Y, Z (general), 1967-1969 (Box 11)
- Alphabetical Series, 1963-1972, bulk 1966-1971; 6
  - A (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - B (general) [1 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 12)
  - B (general) [2 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 12)
  - C (general) [1 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 12)
  - C (general) [2 of 2], 1966-1971 (Box 12)
  - D (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - E (general), 1967-1971 (Box 12)
  - F (general), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fred Gehring, 1963-1969 (Box 12)